(Penny:)That's great.
(clears throat)
(Sheldon:)Wait a minute.
(Sheldon:)I know this may
sound farfetched,
(Sheldon:)but I'm on the market now.
(Sheldon:)You know, if I dated Mandy,
(Sheldon:)that would teach both
Leonard and Amy a lesson.
(Penny:)That's ridiculous.
(Sheldon:)Oh, you're right.
I could never be with a woman
(Sheldon:)whose self-esteem was so low
she'd be with Leonard.
(Penny:)I'm with Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I know. Forever.
(sighs)
(Sheldon:)Who would have believed
these things would happen to us?
Right? (scoffs)
(Penny:)I can't believe Amy
actually went through with it.
(Leonard:)Hang on.
(Sheldon:)You knew that she was
going to end it with me?
(Sheldon:)Did you try
and stop her?
(Penny:)I told her to be true to herself
and do what makes her happy.
(Sheldon:)Do what makes her happy?
(Sheldon:)She plays the harp and
her car is paid for.
(Sheldon:)How much happier can she be?
(Penny:)Okay, look, it's not my fault
(Penny:)that she thought
you were a bad boyfriend.
(Sheldon:)I see.